A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Fellowships, Administration Files, SG 2 FA1226
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Harkness Fellowships - Administration, 1
  - New York Office - Administration - Awards Committee Reports and Correspondence, 1925-1987 (Box 57, Folder 1-31)
  - New York Office - Administration - Awards Committee and Fellows Administration Files, 1933-1982 (Box 58, Folder 1-43)
  - 1991 Harkness Fellows - Final Reports (Box 59, Folder 1-12)
  - 1993 Harkness Fellows - Final Reports, 1993-1994 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - 1994 Harkness Fellows - Final Reports, 1994-1995 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Harkness Fellowship - Final Reports, 1990 (Box 60, Folder 3-23)
  - 1991 Harkness Fellows - Final Reports (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - 1992 Harkness Fellows - Final Reports, 1992-1993 (Box 61, Folder 2-14)
  - 1993 Harkness Fellows - Final Reports, 1993-1994 (Box 61, Folder 15-25)
  - Harkness Fellows Administration Files - Alexander, Spyro Marcus St. John (United Kingdom 1983), 1982-1987 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Harkness Fellows Administration Files - Bartlett, Geoffrey Ray (Australia 1983), 1982-1985 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Harkness Fellows Administration Files - Bone, James (United Kingdom 1983), 1982-1986 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Harkness Fellows Administration Files - Brandenburger, Adam Maurice (United Kingdom 1983), 1982-1986 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Harkness Fellows Administration Files - Broadbent, Richard John (United Kingdom 1983), 1982-1987 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Harkness Fellows Administration Files - Buisson, David H. (New Zealand 1983), 1982-1987 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Harkness Fellows Administration Files - Cook, Helena Mary (United Kingdom, 1983), 1982-1987 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Harkness Fellows Administration Files - Doherty, Richard Ralph (Australia, 1983), 1982-1987 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Harkness Fellows Administration Files - Goodwin, Daisy Georgia (United Kingdom 1983), 1982-1985 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Harkness Fellows Administration Files - Jones, Alexandra Donaldson (United Kingdom 1983), 1982-1989 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Harkness Fellows Administration Files - King, Pauline (New Zealand 1983), 1982-1986 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Harkness Fellows Administration Files - Mills, Stephen Hillary Curwen (Australia 1983), 1982-1986 (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Harkness Fellows Administration Files - Morgan, Jeremy Paul (United Kingdom 1983), 1982-1986 (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Harkness Fellows Administration Files - Parker, Lorna Mary S. (United Kingdom 1983), 1982-1987 (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Harkness Fellows Administration Files - Prior, Elizabeth W. (Australia, 1983), 1982-1985 (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Harkness Fellows Administration Files - Raitt, Suzanne (United Kingdom 1983), 1982-1986 (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Harkness Fellows Administration Files - Rees, Adrian (United Kingdom 1983), 1982-1986 (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - Harkness Fellows Administration Files - Richards, Nigel Gordon John (United Kingdom 1983) (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - Harkness Fellows Administration Files - Smith, Colin Hilton (United Kingdom 1983), 1982-1987 (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - Harkness Fellows Administration Files - Smith, Roland Ralph, 1982-1986 (Box 62, Folder 20)
  - Harkness Fellows Administration Files - Tomlinson, Richard Peter (United Kingdom 1983), 1982-1985 (Box 62, Folder 21)
  - Harkness Fellows Administration Files - Upwards, Christopher Howard Williams (United Kingdom 1983), 1982-1987 (Box 62, Folder 22)
  - Committee Panel Reports and Correspondence, 1970-1995 (Box 63, Folder 1-59)
  - New York Office - Administration - Historical Files, Annual Reports, Trip Reports, Fellows Correspondence and Financial Files, 1925-1982 (Box 64, Folder 1-36)
  - New York Office - Administration - Historical Files, Appointments, Modifications in Fellowship Plan, Fellowship Statistics, 1926-1976 (Box 65, Folder 1-36)
  - New York Office - Administration - Correspondence - Aldrich, Hulbert (Huck), 1968-1977 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - New York Office - Administration - Correspondence - Aldrich, Malcolm P., 1953-1986 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - New York Office - Administration - Correspondence - New Zealand - Burns, Malcolm M., 1961-1986 (Box 66, Folder 3-7)
  - New York Office - Administration - Correspondence - Dean, Patrick, 1969-1980 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - New York Office - Administration - Correspondence - Robson, Hugh, 1968-1978 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - New York Office - Administration - Correspondence - Committee of Award - Burnet, Allistair, 1968-1976 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - New York Office - Administration - Correspondence - Wickman, E. K., 1970-1982 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - New York Office - Administration - Correspondence - Wooster, James, 1972-1980 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - New York Office - Administration - Correspondence - Garretson, Albert Henry, 1984 (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - New York Office - Administration - Correspondence - English, Martha, 1974-1984 (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - New York Office - Administration - Correspondence - Harkness, Edward S., 1927-1928 (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - New York Office - Administration - Minutes, Policy Documents and Correspondence, 1925-1981 (Box 67, Folder 1-11)
  - New York Office - Administration - Unsuccessful, Withdrawn and Reserve Candidates, 1979-1986 (Box 68, Folder 1-42)
  - Correspondence of the New Zealand Selection Committee, 1971-1987 (Box 69, Folder 1-13)
  - Assessment, Project and Board Reports, 1955, 1978-1995 (Box 69, Folder 14-25)
  - Correspondence pertaining to Deceased Fellows, 1926-1990 (Box 70, Folder 1-21)
  - Correspondence pertaining to Deceased Fellows, 1925-1990 (Box 71, Folder 1-11)
  - London Office - Committee Correspondence, 1928-1985 (Box 71, Folder 12-21)
  - London Office - Committee Correspondence, 1925-1984 (Box 72, Folder 1-20)
  - New York Office - Administration - General Correspondence and Administrative Files, 1925-1990 (Box 73, Folder 1-26)
  - New York Office - Administration - Board Reports, 1948-1966 (Box 73, Folder 27-29)
  - New York Office - Administration - Trip Reports, 1958-1969 (Box 73, Folder 30-37)
  - New York Office - Administration - Files pertaining to other International Fellowships, 1925-1941 (Box 73, Folder 38-41)
  - New York Office - Administration - Awards Committee Correspondence; Trip Reports; Finance and Budget Files; Nomination Committee Reports, 1953-1985 (Box 74, Folder 1-29)
  - London Office - Warden's Files, 1949-1967 (Box 75, Folder 1-21)
  - New York Office - Latin American Program - Field Reports, 1940-1946 (Box 76, Folder 1-10)
  - New York Office - Latin American Program - Memos and Applications to Latin American Fellowship Program (Awarded to fellows in South America during World War II) (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - New York Office - Latin American Program - Fellowship Files, 1942-1946 (Box 76, Folder 12-72)
  - New York Office - Historical Files - Fellowships (Budgets, Emoluments, Summaries, Questionnaires), 1925-1980 (Box 77, Folder 1-11)
  - Press Clippings, 1990-1995 (Box 78, Folder 1-8)
  - Rye Orientation Seminar 1996 (Box 78, Folder 9-13)
  - New Orleans 1996 (Box 78, Folder 14)
  - Little Rock, Arkansas 1996 (Box 78, Folder 15)
  - Rye Orientation Seminar 1996 (Box 79, Folder 1-2)
  - Final Reporting Seminar 1996 and 1997, 1996-1997 (Box 79, Folder 3-6)
  - Harkness Fellows 96 - Newletters, 1996 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Harkness Fellows 96 - Advice to Fellows, 1997 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Harkness Fellows 95 - Tucson Seminar, 1995 (Box 79, Folder 9-12)
  - Chicago 96, 1996 (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - Reporting Seminar 1997 (Box 79, Folder 14-15)
  - Brookings Seminar 96, 1996 (Box 79, Folder 16-19)
  - Brookings Seminar 96, 1996 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Brookings Seminar 97, 1997 (Box 80, Folder 2-4)
  - Lotus Club 96, 1996 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - 1984 Fellows Administration Files (United Kingdom) - A-S (Box 80, Folder 6-21)
  - Applications - Austalia, 1998-1999 (Box 81)
  - Applications - New Zealand, 1998-1999 (Box 81)
  - Applications - United Kingdom, 1998-1999 (Box 81)
  - Applications, 1996 (Box 81)
  - 1984 Fellows Administration Files (United Kingdom) - S-Z (Box 82, Folder 1-5)
  - Fellows Administration Files (United Kingdom, Australia, New Zealand)), 1982-1987 (Box 82, Folder 6-23)
  - 1995 Fellows Administration Files - Adminstraion - Hawkins, 1995-1996 (Box 83, Folder 1-3)
  - 1995 Fellows Administration Files - Administration - Lamb, 1995-1996 (Box 83, Folder 4-6)
  - 1995 Fellows Administration Files - Administraiton - Nicholl, 1995-1996 (Box 83, Folder 7-9)
  - 1995 Fellows Administration Files - Administration - Northcott, 1995-1996 (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - 1995 Fellows Administration Files - Administration - Peck, 1995-1996 (Box 83, Folder 11-12)
  - 1995 Fellows Administration Files -Administration - Perese, 1995-1996 (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - 1995 Fellows Administration Files - Administration - Pollock, 1995-1996 (Box 83, Folder 14-16)
  - 1995 Fellows Administration Files - Administration - Rice, 1995-1996 (Box 83, Folder 17)
  - 1995 Fellows Administration Files - Administration - Sayce, 1995-1996 (Box 83, Folder 18-20)
  - 1984 Fellows Administration Files (United Kingdom) - IRS Correspondence (Box 83)
  - Deputy Director Search, 1987-1988 (Box 83)
  - 1995 Fellows Applications, 1995-1996 (Box 83)
  - 1999 Fellows Administration Files - Administration - Australia - Felt, 1999-2000 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - 1999 Fellows Administration Files - Administration - Australia - Piruis, 1999-2000 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - 1999 Fellows Administration Files - Administration - Australia - Homeshaw, 1999-2000 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - 1999 Fellows Administration Files - Administration - Australia - Goldfeld, 1999-2000 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - 1999 Fellows Administration Files - Administration - Australia - Wilton, 1999-2000 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - 1999 Fellows Administration Files - Administration - Australia - Wilcox, 1999-2000 (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - 1999 Fellows Administration Files - Administration - Australia - Lewis, 1999-2000 (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - 1999 Fellows Administration Files - Administration - Australia - Hart, 1999-2000 (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - 1999 Fellows Administration Files - Administration - New Zealand - Thwaites, 1999-2000 (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - 1999 Fellows Administration Files - Administration - New Zealand - Aotearoa, 1999-2000 (Box 85, Folder 10)
  - 1999 Fellows Administration Files - Administration - New Zealand - Hughes, 1999-2000 (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - 1999 Fellows Administration Files - Administration - New Zealand - Keating, 1999-2000 (Box 85, Folder 12)
  - 1999 Fellows Administration Files - Administration - New Zealand - Farquhar, 1999-2000 (Box 85, Folder 13)
  - 1999 Fellows Administration Files - Administration - New Zealand - McTavish, 1999-2000 (Box 85, Folder 14)
  - 1999 Fellows Administration Files - Administration - New Zealand - Crengle, 1999-2000 (Box 85, Folder 15)
  - 1999 Fellows Administration Files - Administration - New Zealand - Johnston, 1999-2000 (Box 85, Folder 16)
  - 1999 Fellows Administration Files - Administration - New Zealand - Cunningham, 1999-2000 (Box 85, Folder 17)
  - 1999 Fellows Administration Files - Administration - United Kingdom - Roe, 1999-2000 (Box 85, Folder 18)
  - 1999 Fellows Administration Files - Administration - United Kingdom - Chin, 1999-2000 (Box 85, Folder 19)
  - 1999 Fellows Administration Files - Administration - United Kingdom - Chin, 1999-2000 (Box 85, Folder 20)
  - 1999 Fellows Administration Files - Administration - United Kingdom - Hughes, 1999-2000 (Box 85, Folder 21)
  - 1999 Fellows Administration Files - Administration - United Kingdom - Findlay, 1999-2000 (Box 85, Folder 22)
  - 1999 Fellows Administration Files - Administration - United Kingdom - Friend, 1999-2000 (Box 85, Folder 23)
  - New York Office - Visitor's Logs (Box 86)
  - New York Office - Press Clippings (Box 86)
  - New York Office - Correspondence - New York and and London Office (In and Out), 1934-1985 (Box 87, Folder 1-18)
  - New York Office - Correspondence, 1924-1977 (Box 88, Folder 1-14)
  - New York Office - Fellows Dinners, 1950-1974 (Box 88, Folder 15)
  - New York Office - Fellows Administration, 1962-1972 (Box 88, Folder 16)
  - New York Office - Press, 1960-1978 (Box 88, Folder 17)
  - 1995 Harkness Fellows Administration Files - Bi-Monthly Reports, 1995-1996 (Box 94, Folder 1-23)
  - Seminar Files - New York City 94, 1994 (Box 95, Folder 1-2, 9-11)
  - Seminar Files - Berkeley 95, 1995 (Box 95, Folder 3-5)
  - Seminar Files - Chicago 95, 1995 (Box 95, Folder 6-8)
  - Administrative Correspondence, 1989 Feburary-March (Box 95, Folder 12-15)
  - Seminar and Conference material, 1991-1993 (Box 96, Folder 1-15)
  - Foundation Fellowship files and Conference files, 1980s-1995 (Box 97, Folder 1-43)
  - 1994 Fellows Reports - Bi-Monthly Reports, 1994-1995 (Box 98, Folder 1-4)
  - 1989, 1990, 1991 Commonwealth Annual Report files, 1990-1992 (Box 98, Folder 5-7)
  - Commonwealth Fund Board Reports, 1989-1992 (Box 98, Folder 8-12)
  - Press Clippings, 1992-1995 (Box 98, Folder 13-17)
  - New Zealand Education Fund, 1995-1996 (Box 99, Folder 30)
  - Australian Fellowship, 1996 (Box 99, Folder 31)
  - Harkness Fellowships Administrative Handbook, 1980s (Box 99, Folder 32-33)
  - Miscellaneous Administrative Files, 1993-1996 (Box 99, Folder 34-36)
  - Miscellaneous Administrative Files, 1993-1996 (Box 100, Folder 1-8)
  - Foundation Fellowship files, A-C, 1980s-1990s (Box 100, Folder 9-36)
  - Foundation Fellowship files, C-G, 1980s-1990s (Box 101, Folder 1-13)
  - Administrative Files and Reports, 1987-1997 (Box 101, Folder 14-19)
  - Harkness Fellows Administration, 1940 (Box 101, Folder 20)
  - Panel of Advisors, 1989 January, April-May (Box 102, Folder 1-2)
  - Seminar Files - Pittsburgh Seminar, 1990 (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - Seminar Files - Brookings Institution Seminar, 1991-1996 (Box 102, Folder 4-11)
  - Placement Advice, 1992-1994 (Box 102, Folder 12-13)
  - Fellows Meetings and Dinenrs, 1994 (Box 102, Folder 14-15)
  - 1985 Fellows Administration Files (United Kingdom and New Zealand), 1985-1986 (Box 103, Folder 1-13)
  - 1986 Fellows Administration Files (United Kingdom and New Zealand), 1986-1987 (Box 103, Folder 14-24)
  - Australia and New Zealand Fellowship Administration Files (Finances, Program Descriptions, Selection, etc.), 1980-1995 (Box 104, Folder 1-48)
  - Australia and New Zealand Fellowship Administration Files and Awards Programs from other Foundations, 1980s-1990s (Box 105, Folder 1-32)
  - Fellows Newsletter files; Harkness Fellowship Publicity; Harkness Fellowship Discretionary Fund files; 65th Anniversary Party, London and Washington, 1980s-1990a (Box 105, Folder 33-54)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence with Fellows, 1990s (Box 106)
  - Fellows Newsletter files; Harkness Fellowship Publicity; Harkness Fellowship Discretionary Fund files; 65th Anniversary Party, London and Washington files, 1980s-1990s (Box 107, Folder 1-19)
  - Fellowships Administrative Correspondence, 1996 January-April (Box 107, Folder 20-27)
  - Fellowships Administrative Correspondence, 1996 April-May (Box 108, Folder 1-4)
  - 1988 Fellows Administrative Files (United Kingdom, Australia, New Zealand) - A-P (Box 108, Folder 5-19)
  - 1988 Fellows Administrative Files (United Kingdom, Australia) - R-W (Box 109, Folder 1-5)
  - 1987 Fellows Administrative Files (United Kingdom, Australia) - A-L (Box 109, Folder 6-17)
  - 1987 Fellows Administrative Files (United Kingdom, Australia) - M-P (Box 110, Folder 1-5)
  - 1985 Fellows Administrative Files (United Kingdom, Australia, New Zealand) - R-W (Box 110, Folder 6-15)
  - 1985 and 1986 Fellows IRS Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 111)
  - Harkness Fellowship Applications, 1980s-1990s (Box 111)
  - 1989 Fellows Administration Files (United Kingdom, Australia, New Zealand) - B-W (Box 112, Folder 1-18)
  - 1990 Fellows Administration Files (United Kingdom, Australia, New Zealand) - B-G (Box 113, Folder 1-10)
  - 1990 Fellows Administration Files (United Kingdom, Australia, New Zealand) - M-S (Box 114, Folder 1-8)
  - Harkness Fellowships Discretionary Fund, 1990-1991 (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - 1991 Fellows Administration Files (United Kingdom, New Zealand) - B-O (Box 114, Folder 10-13)
  - 1991 Fellows Administration Files (United Kingdom, Australia, New Zealand) - A-S (Box 115, Folder 1-15)
  - 1991 Fellows Administration Files (United Kingdom) - S-T (Box 116, Folder 1-2)
  - 1992 Fellows Administration Files (United Kingdom, Australia, New Zealand) - B-M (Box 116, Folder 3-14)
  - 1992 Fellows Administration Files (United Kingdom, Australia, New Zealand) - M-W (Box 117, Folder 1-8)
  - 1993 Fellows Administration Files - D-J (Box 117, Folder 9-15)
  - 1993 Fellows Administration Files - K-T (Box 118, Folder 1-6)
  - 1994 Fellows Administration Files - A-L (Box 118, Folder 7-16)
  - 1994 Fellows Administration Files - L-W (Box 119, Folder 1-12)
  - 1993 Fellows Administration Files - B-C (Box 119, Folder 13-16)
  - 1993 Fellows Administration Files - C (Box 120, Folder 1-2)
  - 1984 and 1985 Fellows - Assessment and Reports, 1984-1985 (Box 120, Folder 3-4)
  - Fellows Adminstration Files - Cornford, James P., 1961 (Box 120, Folder 5)
  - Fellows Administration Files - Wilson, Dierdre S. M., 1968 (Box 120, Folder 6)
  - People, Organizations and Non-Profits - General Files - United Kingdom and United States, 1980s-1990s (Box 120, Folder 7-26)
  - Tax Records - Non-Degree Candidates: Payments for Calendar Year 1967-1973 (Box 121)
  - Great Men and Famous Women (4 vols.), 1894 (Box 121)
    Restricted - Preservation concerns
  - People, Organizations and Non-Profits - General Files - United Kingdom and United States, 1980s-1990s (Box 122, Folder 1)
  - Program Design and Responses from Fellows, 1980s-1990s (Box 122, Folder 2-5)
  - Publicity and Recruitment Files - UK and US, 1989-1995 (Box 122, Folder 6-19)
  - Wearne Associates, 1992-1993 (Box 123, Folder 1-3)
  - General Correspondence and Administrative Files, 1988-1992 (Box 124, Folder 1-29)
  - Payment Requests, 1992 (Box 125)
  - Blacklisted Fellows and IRS Correspondence, 1972-1983 (Box 125)
  - Commonwealth Fund Fellowship Programs - Historical Files, 1925-1949, 1978 (Box 126, Folder 1-4)
  - Classified Directories - British Program, 1925-1957 (Box 126, Folder 5)
  - Commonwealth Fund Fellowships - A Review, 1925-1955, 1957 April (Box 126, Folder 6)
  - Reminiscences, by Richard H. Simpson, first Secretary to the Committee of Award of the Commonwealth Fund Fellowships, 1952 July (Box 126, Folder 7)
  - General Files pertaining to various Institutions and Universities, 1965-1995 (Box 127, Folder 1-46)
  - Exchange Programs, 1986-1993 (Box 128, Folder 1-3)
  - Harkness Report, Vol. 3, No. 1, 1993 (Box 128, Folder 4)
  - Brochures, 1989-1993 (Box 128, Folder 5-6)
  - Postage and Mailing, 1991-1995 (Box 128, Folder 7)
  - Printers, 1992 (Box 128, Folder 8)
  - Fellows Newsletters, 1992-1994 (Box 128, Folder 9)
  - Handbook for Harkness Fellows - Drafts, 1989-1994 (Box 128, Folder 10)
  - Christmas Card Mailings, 1989-1992 (Box 128, Folder 11-13)
  - Harkness Fellows Bulletin, 1993-1994 (Box 128, Folder 14)
  - Directory, 1995 (Box 128, Folder 15)
  - Harkness Report, Vol. 4, No. 1, 1994 (Box 128, Folder 16-17)
  - Harkness Report, Vol. 4, No. 2, 1995 (Box 128, Folder 18)
  - Harkness Report - Printing Bids, 1989-1990 (Box 128, Folder 19)
  - 1995 and 1996 Harkness Fellows - Seminar Files (Indianapolis Seminar), 1995-1996 (Box 129, Folder 1-17)
  - 1995 Harkness Fellows - Arkansas Retreat, 1995-1996 (Box 129, Folder 18-23)
  - 1995 Harkness Fellows - Seminar Files, Tucson, AZ Seminar (Box 129, Folder 24)
  - Harkness Fellows - Seminar Files, New Orleans, LA Seminar, 1996 October (Box 129, Folder 25)
  - Harkness Fellows - Orientation, 1996 August 16-23 (Box 129, Folder 26)
  - 1995 Harkness Fellows - Seminar Files, Tucson, AZ Seminar (Box 130, Folder 1-2)
  - Harkness Fellows - Orientation, 1996 (Box 130, Folder 3)
  - Harkness Fellows - Orientation Seminar Files, Rye, NY, 1995-1996 (Box 130, Folder 4-26)
  - Harkness Fellows - Orientation Seminar Files, Berkeley, CA, 1995 (Box 130, Folder 27-28)
  - Harkness Fellows - Orientation, London, 1995 (Box 130, Folder 29)
  - Harkness Fellows - Retreat, Arizona, 1995 April (Box 130, Folder 30)
- International Health Policy Program (IHP) Administration, 4
  - 93-41 - American Enterprise Institute (AEI) for Public Policy Research - Administration, 1992-1995 (Box 6, Folder 1-6)
  - 93-86 - American Youth Policy Forum, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - 94-83 - American Enterprise Institute (AEI) for Public Policy Research - Administration, 1993-1996 (Box 6, Folder 8-10)
  - 95-21 - Partnership for a Drug Free America (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Sponsor-A-Scholar Philadelphia Futures, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 12-13)
  - 96-147 - Sponsor-A-Scholar Greater Philadelphia, 1995-1997 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - 96949 - Teachers College, Columbia University (Jeannie Brooks-Gunn), 1996 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - 93-86 - Institute for Educational Leadership, 1993-1995 (Box 11, Folder 1-6)
  - 94-64 - Greater Philadelphia Urban Affairs Coalition, Sponsor-A-Scholar Project, 1993-1994 (Box 11, Folder 7-12)
  - 94-80 - Greater Southeast Healthcare System, 1993-1994 (Box 11, Folder 13-16)
  - 94-81 - Jobs for the Future, Inc., 1992-1995 (Box 11, Folder 17-24)
  - International Health Policy Program (IHP) Chronological Files - In and Out, 1997 October-1998 July (Box 22, Folder 1-21)
  - IHP - Chronological Files - In and Out, 1997 May-October (Box 53, Folder 1-15)
  - IHP - Chronological Files - Incoming and Outgoing, 1997 January-May (Box 91)
  - Commonwealth Fund Board Meeting records and preparations, 1997 April (Box 92, Folder 1-7)
  - Commonwealth Fund Board Meeting records and preparations, 1997 July (Box 92, Folder 8-13)
  - Commonwealth Fund Board Meeting records and preparations, 1997 November (Box 92, Folder 14)
- Atlantic Fellowships, 2
  - Atlantic Fellowships - Applications, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 9-26)
  - Nominators, Applicants, and Selection Committee Files, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 1-17)
  - Atlantic Fellowships - Fellows Administration Files, 1996-1999 (Box 19, Folder 1-12)
  - Atlantic Fellowships - Fellows Administration Files, 1996-1999 (Box 19, Folder 14-36)
  - Atlantic Fellowships - Fellows Administration Files, 1996-1999 (Box 19, Folder 38-39)
  - Atlantic Fellowships - Fellows Administration Files, 1996-1999 (Box 19, Folder 13, 37)
  - Brochures, Award Letters, Budget, Finances, Questionnnaires and Nominations, 1995-1999 (Box 20, Folder 1-18)
  - Handbook for Atlantic Fellows, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Publicity-Marketing, Atlantic Fellowships and Staff, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - 1999 Atlantic Fellowship - Applications and Referee Comments, 1998-1999 (Box 47, Folder 1-45)
  - General Administration Files, Applications and Selection Process, 1995-1996 (Box 84)
  - 1998 and 1999 Fellows Applications, 1998-1999, 1999-2000 (Box 89)
  - Short-listed Applicants, 1999 (Box 89)
  - Nominators and Selection (Box 89)
  - 1998 Atlantic Fellows - Budgets, 1997-1999 (Box 90, Folder 1-2)
  - 1998 Atlantic Fellows - Receptions, Meetings (Box 90, Folder 3-5)
  - 1998 Atlantic Fellows - Receptions, Meetings and Orientation, 1998-1999 (Box 90, Folder 6-7)
  - 1997 Atlantic Fellows - Administration (Box 90, Folder 8-23)
  - 1999 Atlantic Fellowships - Brochures; Pamphlets; Nominator Reports and Correspondence; Reception and Orientation Files (Box 93, Folder 1-23)
  - 1995 Atlantic Fellowship - Administration files (Program Description, Budget, Finances, Selection, Timeline), 1995-1996 (Box 99, Folder 1-25)
  - Ian Axford Fellowship - Adminstration files, 1995-1997 (Box 99, Folder 26-29)
  - 1995 Atlantic Fellowship Applications (Box 111)
  - 1994, 1996 and 1997 Atlantic Fellows Administration - Files (Orientation, Sources of Funding, Finances, Seminars, etc.), 1994-1997 (Box 123, Folder 4-25)